http://www.dogzonline.com.au/privacy-policy.asp

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
These terms and conditions apply to the use of the following web sites
www.dogzonline.com.au
www.dogzonline.co.nz
www.dolforums.com.au
Introduction
At Dogz Online, we respect your privacy. We want to maintain your confidence in our handling of any data and information that is collected during your visit to our web site. We have developed and provided this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices and policies regarding the collection, use, maintenance, and disclosure of your personal data and information.
We are committed to providing you with adequate information so you can make an informed decision whether to visit our web site and whether you wish to voluntarily provide any personal data or information, e.g., your name, e-mail address, telephone number, etc. Our Privacy Policy is described in the following sections.
Collection of information
We collect, process and retain personal information from you when you
email us
register for a membership with us
use any of our Services
give us information on a web contact form (eg puppy enquires etc)
update or add information on your membership
join and participate in forum discussions
or when you otherwise contact us.
If you do not agree with this collection of information and the content of this Privacy Policy, we ask that you please do not provide the requested information. You may nevertheless continue to use most of our web site, subject however, to the collection of information through log files as discussed in the 'Log Files' section below.
How we use your information
We use your personal information to
provide and improve our Services
give you a personalised experience on our site
contact you
provide customer service
send you alerts for new ads
let you know of new features on our site
provide you with personalised advertising and marketing
detect, prevent and investigate fraud, spam and/or other illegal activities.
Placing Advertisements
By placing an advertisement on our site (including but not limited to Breeder Listings, Puppy Listings, Classified Ads etc), you give us permission to display that information (including your contact details) publicly on our site for the purposes of promoting your ad.
You also give us permission to reply to any requests for information about your ad or membership that is currently publicly available on our site (or has been previously publicly available).
Using Online Form to Contact Advertisers
Dogs Online analyzes and stores all communications sent to advertisers via our contact form system for the purpose of spotting scams and spam (and blocking these). Do not use our contact form system for any private messages that you may not want us to see. Messages are stored for approximately 6 months.
Log Files
We review data and information contained in log files located on our web server, which record the date and time of each visit to our web site, the user's IP (internet protocol) address, the referring IP address or domain (the prior web site visited), and the files viewed on our web site (including HTML pages, graphics, etc.). We use log file information to analyze data in the aggregate to determine the trends and usage of our site. We can not correlate the log data to identify specific users.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customise Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our sites.
- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....
- Google Adsense
- Amazon
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site to send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
Dogz Online has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Links to Third-Party Web Sites
Through our web pages, you may connect to third parties' web sites via hyperlinks, and the connections may or may not be obvious. We are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. We encourage our users to be aware of the varied privacy policies of web sites that they visit.
Required Disclosures of Data & Information
Regardless of anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may disclose personally identifiable information, with or without prior notice to you, when we believe that the law requires it, in response to subpoenas or at the demand of governmental agencies, to protect our systems or business, to protect other visitors to the web site, or to respond to an emergency. If you partake in, or we reasonably suspect you of partaking in any illegal activity, we may also disclose your personally identifiable information, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order. We may also make disclosures of your personally identifiable information with your affirmative consent.
Maintenance & Transmission of Data & Information
Although we use reasonable efforts to maintain the privacy of your personally identifiable data and information, due to technological limitations, and the risk of unlawful interceptions and accessing of transmissions and/or data, we cannot completely assure you, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable data and information, and any other electronically communicated information, will be absolutely confidential.
For all e-commerce transactions, we use industry-standard commercial encryption technology to protect the data and information that you transmit to us via our web site. We never keep a record anywhere of your full credit card details. (All credit card payments to this site are either processed by paypal or a bank approved payment system).
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Due to changing technological and marketing demands, we reserve the right to change our policies regarding the privacy of your personally identifiable information in the future. If that happens, we will endeavor to promptly update this Privacy Policy. You should review this Privacy Policy periodically so you are updated on any amendments. Your continued use of the web site following changes to this policy will indicate that you accept the changes.
